I'm completely out of cigarettes.
Looks like the world's gone all
blurry from the lack nicotine in me.
Hello there, Yaniko!
I'm the cigarette fairy. When Beastfolk
are in need, I arrive to save them
from the chains of nicotine--
Let go of me you pervert!! Oh, I
need a bath. Reason number two
hundred and fifteen for why I hate
Beastfolk. Friendly tip, Chainsmoker.
I can see you're having a nicotine
overdose, but you're forgetting the
enjoy responsibly in moderation part of
smoking.
That's exactly what I'm doing!
I must say, you sound completely
responsible and in control. Alright.
It would seem we've reached an impasse.
Thus, I shall bestow upon you,
the sacred nicotine receptor exercise!
NICOTINE RECEPTOR EXERCISE
Even her mom's lungs are smokey
Oh, so smokey, oh, so smokey
Oh so smokey
It'll be too late to cry
After she has passed away, yay
Oh, here we go
Here we go, here we go, here we go
Here we go
What do you think? Is it working? Stop!
Don't give in to the nicotine!
It's your fault for shaking that
toasty little booty in my face so don't
run away! Godammit! I can't taste this
cigarette at all!
Of course you can't! After all, I'm just
in your--
Hello? Great. Here.
Fresh newsletter.
After all, I'm nothing more than a
figment of your imagination, Yaniko.
You alright?
No, it can't be. I can feel you right
here with me. Even so, it's nothing
more than an illusion created by
your brain. Don't say that! That's
not true! That's not the smell of smoke,
the feeling of hemp, a sunset reflecting
off the land, and the distant whistle of
a train. Don't you see? I can
never leave this place. We'll be together
forever. So let's do that exercise, Nya?
Nya? Nya?
CHAINSMOKER CAT
Hey, Yaku Neko. I'm running crazy low
on nicotine! Let me bum a smoke off ya!
Oh! Uh, hey. What's up?
Sorry, but if you're looking for
cigs, I'm fresh out.
Liar. You're smoking one right now.
Huh? Oh, yeah. This.
Hmm? Is that not a hand-rolled cig?
Gimme a puff.
Well, the thing is…
Come on! Don't be stingy!
I've treated you to plenty of
my cigarette butts back when you
- were broke.
- Hang on. Wait a sec.
Geez, talk about an ungrateful little
junior.
Oh, but that's not…
Goddamn, that shit's dank!
Oh, man, Senpai? If you're gonna hit it,
you gotta hold that shit in for a sec.
Otherwise, you're wasting the good
stuff, trust me.
Is this a cigarette?
Sure it is.
This is some good stuff you got here,
Yaku!
Shit's gas, right? Oh, Senpai, let's
get some ice cream! It tastes great if
you eat it right now!
This a cigarette?
Course it is.
Chainsmoker Cat.
NOTICE OF MAD BEAST DISEASE SHOT
MAD BEAST PREVENTIVE MEDICATION ENCLOSED
Is it that time of the year already?
I hate how the meds always tastes like
gentian tea.
Yaku, mind if I come in?
What are you doing?
Oh, um, hey! Sup? Howdy?
I wanted to take my Mad Beast prevention
meds but I didn't have any water.
The utilities cut me off again for not
paying.
Uh, yeah! I just took my meds too!
I didn't ask, but okay.
LAXATIVE, SYRINGE, LOZENGE, HERBAL MEDS
VITAMINS, PHONE CARD, WATER
There's no way you're shooting up
any weird drugs again, right?
Of course I'm not doing drugs! I'm clean
now and you fucking know it, don't you?!
Goddammit, Senpai. If you don't believe
me, then who the fuck will? I'll be
all alone. I thought I could just live
like every body else if I finally just
- got clean, but life is bullshit!
- Nya!
Okay, real fast. Quick question for ya.
You care a lot about me, why?
Nya?
Oh, I get it! I know why! You're
a fucking narc, aren't you? Good
disguise, piggy! Now give me back
my senpai, you fucking fed!
Calm down! You're just on a bad
trip, Yaku!
Cops like you are the reason my life's
gone to shit! So just show your true
colors already! Revelio!
YAKU NEKO IS REALLY BAD AT
PROVING HER INNOCENCE
Chainsmoker Cat.
- But, man, that shit was funny, right?
- Yeah, it was good. Good shit's
- Who knew we can drink that much.
- always good.
- Beastfolk, spare a moment of your time?
- For real, though.
The bar owner was fucking crazy man…
Yeah, I didn't think he'd flash his
ass like that in public!
It'll be worth your while!
- Huh?
Looking for excitement? How about a palm
reading?
- Goddamn, that's pricey!
It's probably a waste of time. I'll do
one for a hundred yen though.
I'll consider it for the chance to
wipe those cocky grins off your faces.
That sounds fun.
If you see my truth by the end of the
reading, I want full payment.
That's fine by me.
Hmm, huh?!
Oh, the smell! Forget fortune telling.
Instead, I need to tell you how to
- wash your hands!
- Nya?
- A smoker, I see. You're severely
- Nya.
Addicted and your family longs to
free you from this nicotine curse.
It seems you're a stranger to money, so
you live alone in a slum.
And what's worse, lung cancer will take
you in five years! Or you'll burn alive
from smoking.
Cool it, Senpai! She's just a creepy
old lady! Here you go. Take a big
tasty puff.
Appears, I was correct. Alright,
you're next, Kitty. Don't be afraid.
I'll do yours for a hundred yen.
Huh? Why me? All this kind of "oogie
boogie" stuff is a hard no. Your mystic
mumbo jumbo is based on the Barnum
effect. If ya just open your eyes and
look around you, it's easy to guess stuff
about people.
Are you currently taking any
illegal drugs?
Of course not.
Then do you have a criminal record?
- No way.
- House has never been searched?
- No, never.
- Are you being truthful?
One thousand percent. I don't get it.
Who knew my palm had such a big mouth.
I mean, not like I did anything
wrong though.
You get to decide whether you believe it
or not. If you like what you heard,
just leave a hundred yen and be on
your way.
Hmm…
Huh? Ah!
Chainsmoker Cat!
- Senpai?
- Hmm?
Don't you need to work?
Everything has its time.
My part-time job pays at the end
of each day. You wanna come with?
Listen, Yaku. You see that cloud?
That's what I'm gonna be.
A being of freedom, not bound by the
crudities of our mortal realm. That's
the kind of me that I want to be.
Something as banal as hunger will
never take away that freedom from me.
That's-- That's so cool! You're a buddha,
monk, and stoic sage all wrapped
into one!
Well, I guess even a cloud could get
moving if they ran out of cigarettes.
That's when I'll consider your offer.
Sure! I'll make it happen!
Today's Senpai brings back memories.
Makes me think of when we first met
and how cool you were! That's right, you
were as cool as that cloud in the sky.
And there was nothing in the world
that could hold you down, I loved that.
I know you're in there, Yaku. So open
the fuck up already! Help me get a job,
goddammit! Ah! I know you're not asleep!
You better not be on any fucking
drugs! You hear me?! Wake up and open
- the door!
- What?
It's the middle of the night!
Oh, it's bad. It's really, really bad,
'cause I thought I had a carton, but
I smoked it last week! I need money to
buy cigarettes ASAP! Help me get a
- job so I can start and get paid right
- Woah!
Away! Let me in!
Ah, I get it.
All air and no smoke makes Yaniko a
dull girl, Yaku!
She's not a cloud in the sky.
She's just a cloud of smoke.
Shit.
Shit. Fucking cheater. Oh, come on.
The combo's aren't working! Yeah, just
keep spamming that one move, ya fucking
cheater!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
- You can do better than that, right?
- This game sucks! Hame Neko! This game
fucking sucks!
Fucking sucks!
Lose your temper.
Emotions get in your way. Ya gotta
channel it into focus. Yeah?
If I could do that, I wouldn't
be suffering like this.
It's my turn! I'll teach you how to
play ranked mode matches. I've got
UL-MAS AKA ULTIMATE MASTER RANK
- Sit back and prepare to be wowed.
- Let's do it!
There we go-- No, wait. Crap, uh--
K.O.!
You lose. You must defeat Shen Long to
stand a chance!
You piece of shit, glue-eating,
unga bunga, motherfucker.
Huh?
Anyway, Yani, are you hungry? Why don't
we take a break and make some lunch.
Nya.
Think I got some ramen hiding somewhere.
Nya?
ANGER
By the way, since we're opening up
about our feelings. Would you
quit smoking in the fucking video
game room!
I'm so sorry!
ANGER
I'll kill you, you disgusting fucking
Chimney!
Nya?
And then-- And then! My slipper
went flying.
- Yeah?
- Seriously?! There's no way!
- Wow!
- No, really! I mean it!
You know, you're nothing like any other
Beastfolk I've ever met.
You can let your cat side out with us!
Oh, well, each of us is different when it
comes to stuff like that.
Nya!
- Did you just meow?
- Come on, stop it.
There's the kitty cat!
It's a fluffy, puppy, pup!
It's my cute little sister, Nya!
What's up, Nya? Heading back home from
school, Nya? Yep, I'm her big
sister, Nya!
I didn't know you had a big sis!
I am all about this meowing. She's so
cute.
You not gonna pay attention, Nya?
I'm sorry, have we met?
GETTING READY
PLEASE WAIT
Hey! Hame-hame. Hello, chat! It's time
for Hame-channel, guys! Who's ready?
Hame-chan's so glad everyone came
to watch! By the way, guess what?
I wanted to tell you all, Hame-chan had
something terrible happen to her today!
No! A crane fly?! Ah! Get away from me!
Hame-chan doesn't like flying little
creepy crawlies! You're such a meanie,
Mr. Buggy-Wug! Fine then! I'm gonna
use the vacuum cleaner on you! I'm sowwy,
chat! I gotta stop the stream for
a second!
I can't believe her! I just can't believe
her! She's a complete and utter
embarrassment!
Wow, I didn't know you hated your
sister so much!
I don't hate her!
So you like her then?
Like her? I-- I don't know. I don't
feel too good.
Woah. Sorry, Imoko.
I'm sure its just a complicated
situation, right?
- I don't know!
- Seriously, we're sorry!
Nya!
That's so impressive you can get that
loud, Imoko.
Cigarettes and coffee are a
- perfect match, but I hate how it
- Well, I think "hate" is a bit strong for
- makes me wanna pee.
- me, but…
I do get about it making you wanna pee.
What do you mean? Hame-chan doesn't
understand!
Maybe you two just have hamster-sized
bladders is all?
What do you mean by that, little Miss
Toilet Fairy?
Miss Toilet Fairy? What do you mean
by that?
This girl? In high school? She used to
always eat lunch on the toilet.
We'd try to get her to join us, but she
- wouldn't come out. So, people started
- I am the one possessed by Osiris,
- calling her the Toilet Fairy, or Toir--
- the God of Death.
Stop it!
She'd say, "Leave me alone or
I'll unleash the Eighth Plague of Egypt!"
I'm begging you to please stop
talking about that!
Eighth? Doesn't the second one make more
sense?
No! You're dead!
I mean, Hame-chan is an idol the whole
world looks up to, so she doesn't
do nasty things like peeing, but
Yakuko does.
You heard what she said, Senpai. So, hold
her down for me, okay?
Rub, rub, rub, rub, rub, rub, rub, rub,
- rub, rub, rub, rub, rub, rub, rub, rub,
- Time out, time out, time out, time out!
- Rub, rub,
- Stop, stop, stop, stop! Now's not
- rub, rub, rub, rub, rub, rub, rub, rub,
- the fucking time to do that!
Rub, rub, rub, rub, rub, rub, rub, rub,
rub---
The ol' Eighth Plague of Egypt, huh?
Senpai, this frog looking thing here?
That's the real Toilet Fairy.
Goddamn, you're gross.
I'll kill you, you goddamn motherfucker!
Why is it so bitter and salty?
You fucking junkie! Enjoy the taste of
life itself!
Senpai, I'm gonna puke!
I'm not kidding, here it comes!!
Puke then, you fucking pussy! Puke!
- What?! Is that all you fucking got, you
- Jesus Christ. it's mixing with your
- fucking pussy! Puke! Puke some more!
- piss now! It's in my nose! I can't
You know, I'd really appreciate it
if they didn't do this in my room.
- Puke!
- Breathe!
Chainsmoker Cat.
NYAGAMIHARA CITY HALL
BEASTFOLK CITY NYAGAMIHARA
I went to city hall today.
- Number three hundred and eighty-five?
- Hame Neko's finally getting herself a
- Is three eighty-five still here?
- last name.
- But when both your parents are Beastfolk,
- Number three hundred and eighty-five,
- you don't grow up with one.
- we're ready for you!
She always to get five points knocked
off her grades, 'cause she didn't have
one.
Done! Look, Yannie-nyan! Look! Look!
Hame-chan has a last name!
LAST NAME: YURUFUWA*ANGEL
FIRST NAME: HAMEKO
What is that?
Isn't it the cutest thing ever?!
From now on, Hame's real name is Hameko
Yurufuwa Angel! Nice to meet you,
Yannie-nyan!
I don't know, it's kinda gross. It's long
and kinda hard to say.
What?! You really mean it?
I'm willing to bet nobody will ever say
your full name with a last name
like that.
What?! You meanie! Well then, how come
you've never told me your last name,
Yannie-nyan? I bet it's 'cause it's
a really weird one.
Oh, it's Sato.
That's painfully normal!
I hear it gets way harder to fix your
name after you've already changed it
once, so now's your chance to fix it
before you turn in the paperwork.
I'll be fine! I'm gonna submit it as is!
How's Hameko Tanaka sound?
Oh, hell no!
BEASTFOLK SECTION
CERTIFICATES AND SEAL REGISTRATION
Okay, you should be all set!
You'll receive the official documents in
the mail, so please come back to this
counter to change your Identification
card once you've received them.
Yurufuwa Angel. Hame-chains' finally a
relaxed and fluffy angel.
Crap. Not good, Hame-chan needs a
bathroom.
Nya need to poop?
Just leave me alone!
Um, what do we do in this situation?
Let me take a look. Huh, what's with this
last name. Well, a lot of Beastfolk
have fairly unusual names by our
standards.
This symbol though. Is that a drawing?
What does it mean? She left before I
could ask how to read it.
I wonder what language that could
be, but we can't put any drawings
or symbols into the system.
Oh, I think I got it. It could
possibly be a butthole?
Huh? I guess so. Looks like an anus.
Well then, do I enter "anus" or
"butthole" into the system?
Neither of them flow particularly
well. How bout "anal"?
Maybe I'll do a surprise stream to
celebrate my new last name when
I get home! Hameko Yurufuwa Angel!
And thus, Hameko Yurufuwa Anal Angel
was born.